

## GRANT EMERSON

grant.alex.emerson@gmail.com | (919) 801-8690 | Nashville , TN 37216

### Summary

Passionate, empathetic musician turned web dev with a Full-Stack Web Development Certificate from Vanderbilt University, Experience in JS, React, HTML, CSS, SQL, Sequelize, NoSQL, MongoDB, MERN, SPA utilizing a strong combination of collaboration, communication, leadership, and resultsdriven problem-solving. Proficiency in designing, building and maintaining websites from conception to production. Experienced in graphic design for web content and merchandise. I thrive in a fast-paced and diverse environment prioritizing deadlines as well as deliverables.

#### Skills

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- React
- SQL, NoSQL(MongoDB)
- Node.is
- Photoshop, Affinity Designer
- Instagram, Twitter, Facebook
- Graphic Design
- Squarespace
- Mail Chimp

- Premiere Pro
- Product Design
- Graphic Design
- Guitar
- Product Marketing
- Sales
- SQL
- Web Development

## Experience

#### **Partner**

Delta Rae | Nashville, TN

08/2010 - Current

• Recorded and released three full length records and two EP's: The Light 2020 (Independent), Blackbird Sessions EP 2017 (Big Machine/Valory Records), A Long And Happy Life EP 2017 (Big Machine/Valory Records), After It All 2015 (Warner Brothers Records), Carry The Fire 2012 (Warner Brothers Records).

01/2020 - Current **Creative Designer** 

Nashville Running Company | Nashville, TN

- Sales, graphic design, social media management, content creation, product marketing, product design, marketing campaign creation.
- Developed and maintain eCommerce, Shopify storefront.

#### Owner, sole operator

05/2018 - Current

HUMANGOODKIND | Nashville, TN

- Humangoodkind is a social justice T-shirt company.
- A portion of proceeds are donated to different charities and/or causes.
- I do all the graphic design and social media management.

**Guitar Instructor** 01/2008 - 12/2010

Cary School Of Music | Cary, NC

- Led guitar lessons for students of diverse demographics.
- Built trusting rapport with students and facilitated communication with family members when needed.
- Planned lessons according to student skill level and learning modality.

# Education and Training

## Full-Stack Web Development Certificate

Vanderbilt University | Nashville, TN

Bachelor: General Music

University of North Carolina at Wilmington | Wilmington, NC

2020

2008